Guide to the Islamic Fundamentalist Audio Recordings Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Tape 308. A sermon on supplication to God, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 308)
  ????? ?????: ????? ????? ?? ?????? ??? ???? ?? ??? ??????? ??????? ???????? ??? ???? ???????. ???? ??????? ??? ?????? ????? ????? ?? ?????? ?? ???? ???? ??? ????? ?????
  ????? ??????: ???? ??????? ????? ? ???? ??? ?????? ??? ???????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 309. A sermon on good deeds, 1994; 1 (Box 309)
  Comments: Side A 31:06 min. Side B 31:20 min. Speaker: Ibra?hi?m ibn ?Abd Alla?h al-Duwaysh.
  Side A: A recording of a sermon on good deeds that must be faithfully carried out by Muslims in the faith of God and not for worldly purposes. The speaker cites Ibn Taymi?yah's advisory opinion in this issue.
  Side B: The speaker tells stories about asceticism and good deeds.
  ?????????: ??? ????? ????? 31:06 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 31:20 ?????. ???????: ??????? ?? ??? ???? ??????
  ????? ?????: ????? ????? ?? ????? ?????? ???? ??? ?? ???? ?? ?????? ?????? ????? ??? ???? ???? ?????? ??????. ?????? ??????? ???? ??? ????? ?? ??? ???????
  ????? ??????: ???? ??????? ????? ?? ????? ??????? ?????? ??????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 310. A sermon addressed to the Muslim youth, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 310)
  [Duplicate of Tape 302].
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 311. A sermon on adultery, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 311)
  Comments: The speaker stammers. Side A 47:09 min. Side B 45:52 min.
  Side B: A recording of a sermon on adultery: the reason it's prohibited and its legitimate punishment. The speaker rejects mixing of men and women. The recording cuts off at the end of side B.
  ?????????: ??????? ????? ?? ??????. ??? ????? ????? 47:09 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 45:52 ?????
  ????? ??????: ????? ????? ?? ?????, ??? ?????? ??????? ???????. ???? ??????? ???????? ??? ?????? ???????. ????? ??????? ?????? ????? ??????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 312. A recitation from and interpretation of the Qur?a?n, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 312)
  Comments: Audio quality is very poor especially on side A. Side A 31:27 min. Side B 30:36 min.
  Side A: This side starts with background noise then a recording of a speaker who recites verses from the Qur?a?n and followed by another speaker who interprets these verses.
  Side B: The speaker continues the interpretation of the verses and answers questions from the audience. From 11:24 a recitation from the Qur?a?n of Surat al-Ma??idah verses 114-120 and al-An?a?m verses 1-67.
  ?????????: ????? ????? ????? ???? ???? ?? ?????? ?????. ??? ????? ????? 31:27 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 30:36 ?????
  ????? ?????: ???? ?????? ?? ????? ???? ???? ???? ?? ?????? ???? ???????? ???? ??? ??? ?????? ??? ??????
  ????? ??????: ???? ??????? ????? ?????? ????? ?? ????? ??????. ?? 11:24 ????? ?? ?????? ????? ??????? ????? 114 ??? 120 ???????? ????? 1 ??? 67
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 313. A sermon on fate and divine decree, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 313)
  Comments: Side A 29:25 min. Side B 29:24 min.
  Side A: A recording of a sermon on fatalism. The speaker reviews advisory opinions of some Salafi? scholars on fate and divine decree and explains these opinions to the audience.
  Side B: The speaker reads verses of poetry to the audience on fate and divine decree. Other speakers talk about fatalism and patience in the face of calamity.
  ?????????: ??? ????? ????? 29:25 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 29:24 ?????
  ????? ?????: ????? ????? ?? ??????? ??????? ??????. ?????? ??????? ???? ????? ???? ?? ????? ??????? ??? ????? ?????? ?????? ??????? ??????
  ????? ??????: ???? ??????? ????? ?? ????? ?????? ?? ?????? ??????. ????? ??????? ????? ?? ??????? ??????? ?????? ?????? ??? ???? ??????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 314. A sermon on the elements of power of life, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 314)
  Comments: Recording is faint and audio is unintelligible on most parts of the audio tape. Side A 44:56 min. Side B 44:53 min. Speaker: ?Abd al-Rah?ma?n ibn Muh?ammad al-Dawsari?.
  Side A: The speaker talks about his belief in the elements of power of life and explains each to the audience.
  Side B: The speaker calls to uphold the elements of power which he had mentioned and explained.
  ?????????: ??????? ???? ?????? ??? ????? ?? ???? ????? ??????. ??? ????? ????? 44:56 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 44:53 ?????. ???????: ??? ?????? ??? ???? ???????
  ????? ?????: ????? ??????? ?? ?????? ?? ????? ????? ?? ?????? ??????? ????? ???? ???? ??????
  ????? ??????: ???? ??????? ??? ?????? ?????? ????? ???? ????? ??????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 315. Q&A session on different issues, Date: Circa 1979-2000; 1 (Box 315)
  Comments: Audio quality is very poor. Side A 31:13 min. Side B 31:13 min.
  Side A: A recording of Q&A session on different issues such as Jihad and establishing Islamic state in Afghanistan, the Islamic revolution in Iran, a revolution in Afghanistan, and watching television.
  Side B: The same speaker answers more questions on Jihad in Afghanistan, the commitment of Muslim youth to religion, and other issues.
  ?????????: ????? ????? ????? ????. ??? ????? ????? 31:13 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 31:13 ?????
  ????? ?????: ????? ?????? ?????? ?? ?????? ??? ?????? ?????? ???? ??????? ?? ?????????, ?????? ????????? ?? ?????, ?????? ?? ?????????, ?????? ????????? ??????
  ????? ??????: ???? ??? ??????? ?? ???? ?? ??????? ?? ?????? ??? ?????? ?? ?????????, ?????? ?????? ?????? ??????? ?????, ??????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 316. A lecture on self resistance to desires and passions, 1974; 1 (Box 316)
  Comments: Background noise but audio is intelligible. Side A 44:50 min. Side B 44:50 min. Speaker: ?Abd al-Rah?ma?n ibn Muh?ammad al-Dawsari?.
  Side A: A recording of a lecture on self resistance to desires and passions. The speaker interprets verses from the Qur?a?n on related to this issue. From 22:50 another recording for the same speaker in which he reads a poem.
  Side B: The speaker preaches on Jihad and answers questions from the audience.
  ?????????: ???? ????? ??? ????? ?????. ??? ????? ????? 44:50 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 44:50 ?????. ???????: ??? ?????? ??? ???? ???????
  ????? ?????: ????? ??????? ?? ???? ????? ??????? ??????? ????????. ???? ??????? ???? ?? ?????? ??????? ?????? ???? ?????. ?? 22:50 ????? ??? ???? ??????? ???? ??? ????? ?? ?????
  ????? ??????: ???? ??????? ????? ?? ?????? ? ???? ?? ????? ??????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 317. A lecture on migration in Islam, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 317)
  Comments: Side A 43:43 min. Side B 43:45 min.
  Side A: A recording of a lecture on the migration of Muslims at the time of the Prophet. The speaker addresses the issue of correlation of Islam with politics. He believes that separation of religion from politics is the reason of Muslims' weakness.
  Side B: The speaker talks about the need of the promotion of virtue and prevention of vice and establishing an Islamic state.
  Summary (Arabic
  ?????????: ??? ????? ????? 43:43 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 43:45 ?????
  ????? ?????: ????? ??????? ?? ?????? ???????? ?? ??? ??????. ?????? ??????? ???? ?????? ????? ???????? ???????? ?????? ??? ??? ????? ?? ??????? ?? ??? ??? ????????
  ????? ??????: ????? ??????? ?? ???? ????? ????????? ?????? ?? ?????? ??????? ??? ???? ???? ???????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 318. A lecture on migration in Islam, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 318)
  [Duplicate of Tape 317].
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 319. A lecture on self resistance to desires and passions, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 319)
  [Duplicate of Tape 316].
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 320. A speech about progressive regimes, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 320)
  Comments: Background noise and audio quality is poor. Side A 43:44 min. Side B 43:42 min.
  Side A: A recording of a speech about the progressive regimes, racial discrimination in some countries such as the United States and India, communism, and other varied subjects. The speaker answers questions from the audience on different jurisprudential issues.
  Side B: The speaker talks about the Islamic conquests for several countries and the consequent dissemination of the Islamic concepts and civilization.
  ?????????: ???? ????? ?????? ????? ?????. ??? ????? ????? 43:44 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 43:42 ?????
  ????? ?????: ????? ????? ?? ??????? ????????, ??????? ??????? ?? ??? ??????? ??? ???????? ??????? ??????, ????????? ?????? ?? ??????? ????????. ???? ??????? ?? ????? ?????? ?? ????? ????? ??????
  ????? ??????: ????? ??????? ?? ???????? ????????? ?????? ?????? ??? ???? ???? ?? ??? ??????? ????????? ????????? ??? ??? ????????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 321. Q&A session on jurisprudential issues, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 321)
  Comments: Side A 31:16 min. Side B 31:44 min.
  Side A: Duplicate of Tape 315, Side B.
  Side B: Duplicate of Tape 315, Side A.
  ?????????: ??? ????? ????? 31:16 ?????. ??? ????? ??????
  ????? ?????: ????? ????? ?????? ?? ?????? ??? 315
  ????? ??????: ????? ????? ????? ?? ?????? ??? 315
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 322. A sermon on the Islamic religion, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 322)
  Comments: Audio quality is poor. Side A 31:33 min. Side B 31:35 min.
  Side A: A recording of a sermon on the Islamic religion in which the speaker explains some of the teachings, objectives, and requirements of Islamic religion.
  Side B: The speaker talks about the prohibition of seeking help from the "infidels", such as military assistance. The recording cuts off at the end of side B.
  ?????????: ????? ????? ?????. ??? ????? ????? 31:33 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 31:35 ?????
  ????? ?????: ????? ????? ?? ????? ???????? ???? ???? ??????? ??? ??????, ????? ? ??????? ????? ????????
  ????? ??????: ????? ??????? ?? ????? ??? ????? ?? "??????" ?????? ????????? ????????. ????? ??????? ?????? ????? ??????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 323. A sermon on the divine mercy, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 323)
  Comments: Side A 46:50 min. Side B 47:25 min.
  Side A: A recording of a sermon on the divine mercy. The speaker explains that application of mercy among humans is a divine order but conditioned with establishment of an Islamic state in order to be achieved. He criticizes the opinions of some Islamic scholars in introducing and defining Islam especially to the West.
  Side B: The speaker answers different questions from the audience.
  ?????????: ??? ????? ????? 46:50 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 47:25 ?????
  ????? ?????: ????? ????? ?? ?????? ???????. ???? ??????? ??? ????? ?????? ??? ????? ?? ??? ???? ?????? ????? ???? ??????? ?????? ?????? ?????? ??? ?????. ????? ??????? ???? ??? ???????? ?????????? ?? ??????? ???????? ???????? ?????? ?????
  ????? ??????: ???? ??????? ?? ????? ?????? ?? ??????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 324. A sermon on God's piety, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 324)
  Comments: Side A 21:49 min. Side B 20:42 min.
  Side A: A recording of a sermon on God's piety which includes reading and interpreting verses from the Qur?a?n, stories, and Hadiths pertinent to this subject.
  Side B: A recording of another sermon which includes reading and interpreting verses from the Qur?a?n. From 13:42 recitation from the Qur?a?n of Surat al-Ja?thiyah verses 24-37 and al-Ah?qa?f verses 1-12.
  ?????????: ??? ????? ????? 21:49 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 20:42 ?????
  ????? ?????: ????? ????? ?? ???? ???? ????? ????? ???? ?? ?????? ???????? ???? ? ?????? ?? ?????? ??????? ??? ??? ???????
  ????? ??????: ????? ????? ???? ?? ?????? ????? ????? ?????? ?? ?????? ???????? ????????. ?? 13:42 ????? ?? ?????? ????? ??????? ????? 24 ??? 37 ? ??????? ????? 1 ??? 12
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 325. A sermon on the pillars of faith, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 325)
  Comments: Sound quality is very poor. Side A 46:18 min. Side B 44:19 min.
  Side A: A recording of a sermon on the pillars of faith such as pilgrimage (al-h?ajj). The speaker defines pilgrimage (al-h?ajj), its reasons, and the origin of this obligation. The speaker talks about the origin of Arabs, the prophetic messages, and the prophets sent by God to the Arab people in the Arab peninsula.
  Side B: The speaker continues his sermon and talks about commitment to the Islamic teachings as they appeared in the Qur?a?n and Hadith and the need to avoid all that was forbidden by God and the Prophet. From 31:50 a recitation from the Qur?a?n of Surat al-Ja?thiyah verses 24-37 and al-Ah?qa?f verses 1-26.
  ?????????: ????? ????? ????? ????. ??? ????? ????? 46:18 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 44:19 ?????
  ????? ?????: ????? ????? ?? ????? ??????? ????? ????. ???? ??????? ??????? ???? ??????? ???? ??? ???????. ????? ??????? ?? ??? ????? ? ???????? ??????? ????????? ????? ????? ???? ??? ????? ?? ??????? ???????
  ????? ??????: ???? ??????? ?????? ?????? ?? ???????? ??????? ??????? ???? ???? ?? ?????? ??????? ??????? ?? ?? ??? ??? ???? ???????. ?? 31:50 ????? ?? ?????? ????? ??????? ????? 24 ??? 37 ? ??????? ????? 1 ??? 26
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 326. Q&A session on Jurisprudential issues, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 326)
  Comments: Side A 31:19 min. Side B 29:49 min.
  Side B: A recording of Q&A session on prayer and on the Islamic punishment of theft by cutting off the hand of the burglar. From 14:40 recording is faint and audio is unintelligible. Background noise from 19:00 to the end of side B.
  ?????????: ??? ????? ????? 31:19 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 29:49 ?????
  ????? ??????: ????? ?????? ?????? ?? ?????? ?????? ?????? ???? ?? ?????? ???? ??? ????? ? ?? ??????. ?? 14:40 ??????? ???? ?????? ??? ?????. ????? ?? 19:00 ??? ????? ????? ??????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 327. A sermon on adultery, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 327)
  [Duplicate of Tape 311].
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 328. A poetry reading, Circa 1984-2000; 1 (Box 328)
  Comments: Side A 45:42 min. Side B 45:42 min. Speaker: ?Ashma?wi?, ?Abd al-Rah?ma?n S?a?lih?. Place: Saudi Arabia.
  Side A: A recording of a poetry reading by an Islamic poet. The poet reads a number of poems in which he criticizes the situation of the Islamic nation.
  Side B: The speaker reads more poems about the situation of the Islamic nation, women, and speaks about Islamic literature.
  ?????????: ??? ????? ?????: 45:42 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 45:42 ?????. ???????: ??? ?????? ???? ????????. ??????: ????????
  ????? ?????: ????? ?????? ????? ????? ??????. ???? ?????? ?????? ????? ????? ???? ??? ????? ?????????
  ????? ??????: ???? ??????? ????? ???? ?? ??? ????? ????????? ? ?????? ?????? ?? ????? ????????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 329. Q&A session on different issues, Circa 1979-1991; 1 (Box 329)
  Comments: Audio quality is poor. Side A 30:56 min. Side B 30:53 min.
  Side A: A recording of Q&A session on different issues such as times of supplication, the situation of Muslims in the former Soviet Union, the Islamic ruling on men's clothes, and the advantages of reading.
  Side B: The speaker answers some questions about the Islamic revolution in Iran, a revolution in Afghanistan, watching television, and prayer. From 19:20 a recording of a sermon on migration in Islam. The recording cuts of at the end of side B.
  ?????????: ????? ????? ?????. ??? ????? ????? 30:56 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 30:53 ?????
  ????? ?????: ????? ?????? ?????? ?? ?????? ??? ????? ??????, ??? ???????? ?? ??????? ???????? ??????, ????? ?????? ??????? ??????, ?????? ???????
  ????? ??????: ???? ??? ??????? ?? ???? ?? ??????? ?? ?????? ??? ?????? ????????? ?? ?????, ?????? ?? ?????????, ?????? ?????????, ???????. ?? 19:20 ????? ????? ?? ?????? ?? ???????. ????? ??????? ?????? ????? ??????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 330. A sermon on Muslim women, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 330)
  Comments: Side A 30:40 min. side B 31:09 min.
  Side A: A recording of a sermon on Muslim women and their role and place in society, marriage, and the high cost of dowry. The speaker narrates stories about the wives of the Prophet and advices the Muslim wives on education and work. From 26:10 the speaker leads a congregational prayer with the audience.
  Side B: A recording of another sermon by the same speaker on Muslim women. The speaker advises the Muslim women to commit to the teachings of Islam as they appeared in the Qur?a?n and to disregard the calls for women's liberty and equality with men. From 22:30 the speaker leads a congregational prayer with the audience.
  ?????????: ??? ????? ????? 30:40 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 31:09 ?????
  ????? ?????: ????? ????? ?? ?????? ??????? ?????? ???????? ?? ??????? ??????? ????? ??????. ???? ??????? ????? ?? ??? ????? ?????? ????? ????? ??? ??????? ???????? ??? ?????? ??????. ?? 26:10 ???? ??????? ?? ?????? ???? ???????
  ????? ??????: ????? ????? ???? ?? ??? ??? ??????? ?? ?????? ???????. ???? ??????? ??????? ??? ?????? ???????? ????????? ??????? ????? ???????? ??? ??? ?? ?????? ???? ??????? ??? ????? ???? ?????? ????????? ??? ?????? ??????. ?? 22:30 ???? ??????? ?? ?????? ???? ???????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 331. A recitation from the Qur?a?n, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 331)
  Comments: Side A 30:54 min. Side B 30:57 min.
  Side A: A recitation from the Qur?a?n of Sura al-Kahf verses 1-34.
  Side B: A recitation from the Qur?a?n of Sura al-Kahf verses 31-38. From 4:00 a recitation from the Qur?a?n of Sura al-Shu?ra? verses 1-25.
  ?????????: ??? ????? ????? 30:54 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 30:57 ?????
  ????? ?????: ????? ?? ?????? ????? ????? ????? 1 ??? 34
  ????? ??????: ????? ?? ?????? ????? ????? ????? 31 ??? 38. ?? 4:00 ????? ?? ?????? ????? ?????? ????? 1 ??? 25
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 332. A recitation from the Qur?a?n, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 332)
  Comments: Side A 27:52 min. Side B 27:51 min. Speaker: ?Abd al-Rah?ma?n al-Sudays.
  Side A: A recitation from the Qur?a?n of Surat Maryam verses 1-98 and T?a?ha? verses 1-97.
  Side B: A recitation from the Qur?a?n of Surat T?a?ha? verses 98-135 and al-Anbiya?? verses 1-112. From 25:10 a recording of a prayer.
  ?????????: ??? ????? ????? 27:52 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 27:51 ?????. ???????: ??? ?????? ??????
  ????? ?????: ????? ?? ?????? ????? ???? ????? 1 ??? 98 ? ?? ????? 1 ??? 97
  ????? ??????: ????? ?? ?????? ????? ?? ????? 98 ??? 135 ? ???????? ????? 1 ??? 112. ?? 25:10 ????? ?????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 333. A lecture on Islam, Circa 1979-2000; 1 (Box 333)
  Comments: Side A 46:17 min. Side B 24:56 min. Speaker: Jum?ah ?Ali? al-Khu?li?.
  Side A: The lecture starts with a recitation from the Qur?a?n of Sura Fus?s?ilat verses 30-36 followed by an introduction to the speaker. Then the speaker gives a lecture on the continuity of Islam in which he explains in detail the meaning of the word "Islam" and speaks about the beginning of the Islamic message and its continuity and dissemination through the Islamic conquests.
  Side B: The speaker talks about resistance and rejection of the Muslim countries and people to the military and cultural invasion. He believes that Islam is the major motivation to the liberation movements and revolutions in the Arabic and Muslim countries.
  ?????????: ??? ????? ????? 46:17 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 24:56 ?????. ???????: ???? ??? ??????
  ????? ?????: ???? ???????? ?????? ?? ?????? ????? ????? ????? 30 ??? 36 ?? ????? ?????? ??????? ???????. ???? ????? ??????? ?????? ?? ????????? ??????? ???? ???? ???????? ?????? ?????? ?????? ??????? ?????? ?? ????? ??????? ????????? ???????????? ????????? ?????? ???????? ?????????
  ????? ??????: ????? ??????? ?? ?????? ??????? ??????? ????????? ?????? ????? ??????? ???????? ?????? ?? ??????? ?? ?????? ??????? ?????? ?????? ???????? ?? ????? ??????? ??????????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 334. A lecture on the interpretation of the Qur?a?n, Circa 1973-1978; 1 (Box 334)
  Comments: Background noise but audio is intelligible. Side A 31:04 min. Side B 20:35 min.
  Side A: A recording of a lecture on the interpretation of the Qur?a?n. the speaker explains the meaning and types of interpretations. He addresses the issue of understanding the meanings in the Qur?a?n in addition to reading and memorizing it by studying the Qur?a?nic texts with reference to the books of interpretations.
  Side B: The speaker addresses and criticizes the interpretation of the Qur?a?n by some of Islamic sects such as Sufis and by some interpreters such as al-Ra?zi?.
  ?????????: ???? ????? ??? ????? ?????. ??? ????? ????? 31:04 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 20:35 ?????
  ????? ?????: ????? ??????? ?? ????? ??????. ???? ??????? ???? ??????? ????? ??????. ????? ?? ????? ???? ?????? ???????? ??? ?????? ????? ?? ???? ????? ????? ?????? ???????? ??????? ??? ????????
  ????? ??????: ?????? ??????? ?????? ????? ?????? ?? ??? ??? ????? ???????? ????????? ??? ??????? ???? ???????? ??? ??????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 335. A lecture on education, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 335)
  Comments: Side A 30:33 min. Side B 29:30 min.
  Side A: A speaker gives a lecture on particularly religious education and speaks about the role of the Prophet Muh?ammad in delivering and teaching the message of Islam to people.
  Side B: The speaker continues his lecture and talks about the role of the Prophet Muh?ammad in teaching Islamic religion to people, cites verses from the Qur?a?n and Hadiths, and answers questions from the audience. From 21:48 a recitation from the Qur?a?n of Sura al-An?a?m verses 1-10.
  ?????????: ??? ????? ????? 30:33 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 29:30 ?????
  ????? ?????: ???? ??????? ?????? ?? ??????? ???????? ??????? ?????? ?????? ?? ??? ?????? ???? ?? ????? ??????? ????????? ??????? ???????? ?????
  ????? ??????: ????? ??????? ??????? ?? ??? ?????? ???? ?????? ????? ????? ???????? ???????? ??????? ????? ?? ?????? ??????? ????? ????? ?? ????? ??????. ?? 21:48 ????? ?? ?????? ????? ??????? ????? 1 ??? 10
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 336. A sermon on passion, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 336)
  Comments: Side A 44:23 min. Side B 35:40 min.
  Side A: A recording of a sermon on passion, its definition in the Qur?a?n, its treatment, and the reviews of some Islamic scholars of this subject. The speaker narrates stories and tells some advisory opinions pertinent to this subject.
  Side B: The speaker talks about lust and adoration as some of the reasons for deviation from the Islamic religion, their impact on humans, and how to resist them.
  ?????????: ??? ????? ????? 44:23 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 35:40 ?????
  ????? ?????: ????? ????? ?? ?????, ????? ?????? ??, ?????, ?????? ????? ???????? ???? ???????. ???? ??????? ????? ????? ????? ???? ?? ??????? ?? ??? ???????
  ????? ??????: ????? ??????? ?? ?????? ?????? ???????? ??? ?? ????? ???????? ?? ????? ???????? ?????? ?? ??????? ??? ??????? ? ????? ?????????
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2
- Tape 337. A recitation from the Qur?a?n, Circa 1965-2000; 1 (Box 337)
  Comments: Side A 42:39 min. Side B 43:46 min.
  Side A: A recitation from the Qur?a?n of Surat Yu?suf verses 68-111; al-Ra?d verses 1-43, and Ibra?hi?m verses 1-27.
  Side B: A recitation from the Qur?a?n of Surat Ibra?hi?m verses 28-52, al-H?ijr verses 1-99, and al-nah?l verses 1-78.
  ?????????: ??? ????? ????? 42:39 ?????. ??? ????? ?????? 43:46 ?????
  ????? ?????: ????? ?? ?????? ????? ???? ????? 68 ??? 111 ? ????? ????? 1 ??? 43 ? ??????? ????? 1 ??? 27
  ????? ??????: ????? ?? ?????? ????? ??????? ????? 28 ??? 52 ? ????? ????? 1 ??? 99 ? ????? ????? 1 ??? 78
  - Preservation masters, 2
  - Use copies, 2